I learned that schizophrenic hallucinations are shaped by culture.
So apparently in the United States, the voices are harsher and more threatening.
But in Africa and India, they're more benign and playful.
Isn't that fascinating?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And also terrible at the same time.
I also learned this week that birdsong is relaxing for a reason that I think a lot of us would not know.
So apparently the most accurate answer for why birdsong is actually associated with relaxing
is because it goes back hundreds of thousands of years and is found in the evolution of our nervous system.
Apparently most birds only sing when there's no danger.
So humans, as we evolved, came to subconsciously relate birds singing with safety.
So this one I thought was really timely.
Fifty-six years ago, on April 23rd, Columbia University in New York City had students revolt on campus.
Sound familiar?
Yeah.
Occupying school buildings and disrupting class to protest the school's ties to the Vietnam War and racism in New York.
One of the hosts of Democracy Now!, Juan Gonzalez, participated in the 1968 protests
when hundreds of students were injured by police and arrested.
And he speaks about it on Democracy Now!, about the rebellion and how it compares to Columbia's crackdown
on pro-Palestinian protesters today.
So make sure you check that out.
We up, we up, we up.
We up.